<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="https://cdn.mysitemapgenerator.com/api/feedpreview_s.8165aa1a3b639b5a75d978efdd709ae9.xsl"?>
		<!--	created with www.mysitemapgenerator.com	-->
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
	<channel>
		<title>phonespecpro.com</title>
		<link><![CDATA[https://phonespecpro.com/]]></link>
		<description>Explore phone specifications, reviews, and comparisons of the latest smartphones. Compare camera, battery, performance, and prices to find the best phone for you.</description>
		<language>en</language>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 11:49:04 +0000</pubDate>
		<generator>MySitemapGenerator (www.mysitemapgenerator.com)</generator>

		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">3538181953</guid>
			<title>Motorola Edge 70 India Launch Set for December 15</title>
			<link>https://phonespecpro.com/news/motorola-edge-70-india-launch-december-15</link>
			<author>shedrack</author>
			<description>Motorola confirms Edge 70 launch in India on December 15. Get specs, features, price, and availability details for the ultra-thin 5.99mm smartphone.</description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>By: <a href="https://phonespecpro.com/author/shedrack">Shedrack</a></p><p><img src="https://phonespecpro.com/img/motorola-edge-70-india-launch-december-15.webp"></p><h2>Official Launch Announcement</h2><p>Motorola has officially confirmed that the much-anticipated Edge 70 will launch in India on December 15, 2025 . The company began teasing the device last week and has now solidified the date, with sales commencing on the same day through Flipkart, the Motorola online store, and other major retailers.</p><p>This launch marks the Indian debut of Motorola's thinnest smartphone yet, which aims to compete in the premium mid-range segment with its blend of sleek design and capable hardware.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 12:49:03 +0100</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://phonespecpro.com/img/motorola-edge-70-india-launch-december-15.webp" />
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">1547150418</guid>
			<title>Nothing OS 4.0 Rollout Paused as Company Works on 'Urgent' Fix</title>
			<link>https://phonespecpro.com/news/nothing-os-4-rollout-paused-urgent-fix</link>
			<author>shedrack</author>
			<description>Nothing has paused the Android 16-based Nothing OS 4.0 rollout for its smartphones to implement an urgent fix, delaying the update for Phone 3, Phone 2, and other models.</description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Your ultimate destination for comprehensive phone specifications, comparisons, and reviews.</p><h3>Quick Links</h3><h3>About Us</h3><p>© 2025 PhoneSpec Pro. All rights reserved.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 12:49:02 +0100</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://phonespecpro.com/img/nothing-os-4-rollout-paused-urgent-fix.webp" />
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">3375614065</guid>
			<title>Vivo S50 and S50 Pro Mini Launch Date Confirmed; Color Options Revealed</title>
			<link>https://phonespecpro.com/news/vivo-s50-s50-pro-mini-launch-date-colors</link>
			<author>shedrack</author>
			<description>Vivo S50 series launch confirmed for December 15 in China. Check specs, color options, and features for S50 and S50 Pro Mini.</description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>By: <a href="https://phonespecpro.com/author/shedrack">Shedrack</a></p><p><img src="https://phonespecpro.com/img/vivo-s50-s50-pro-mini-launch-date-colors.webp"></p><h2>Official Launch Announcement</h2><p>Vivo has officially confirmed that its new S50 series smartphones will launch in China on December 15, 2025 . The launch event is scheduled for 7:00 PM local time (4:30 PM IST) and will introduce two models: the standard Vivo S50 and the more compact flagship, the Vivo S50 Pro Mini.</p><p>Following weeks of teasers on Chinese social media platform Weibo, the company has also opened pre-reservations for the devices through its official online store in China, generating significant anticipation for this camera-focused series.</p><h2>Confirmed Color Options</h2><p>Ahead of the launch, Vivo has officially revealed the color variants for both new phones through its online store. The choices emphasize a premium and serene aesthetic.</p><p>Vivo S50 Colors Confession White, Inspirational Purple, Space Black, and Serene Blue.</p><p>Vivo S50 Pro Mini Colors Confession White, Inspirational Purple, and Space Black.</p><h2>Key Specifications & Features</h2><p>Processor Qualcomm Snapdragon 8 Gen 5 chipset. Expected to feature the Snapdragon 8s Gen 3 chipset.</p><p>Display 6.31-inch flat AMOLED display. Compact flagship size. 6.59-inch flat OLED display with 1.5K resolution and 120Hz refresh rate.</p><p>Camera (Highlight) Triple rear camera with a 50MP Sony IMX882 periscope telephoto lens. 50MP front camera. Expected to feature a 50MP Sony IMX882 periscope telephoto camera. Rumored 50MP selfie camera.</p><p>RAM & Storage LPDDR5X RAM and UFS 4.1 storage. Configurations up to 16GB+512GB. LPDDR5X RAM and UFS 4.1 storage. Multiple configurations expected.</p><p>Battery & Charging 6,500mAh battery with 90W wired and 40W wireless fast charging support. Expected to support 90W fast charging. Battery size not yet detailed.</p><p>Software Expected to run Android 16-based OriginOS 6. Expected to run Android 16-based OriginOS 6.</p><p>Other Features Ultrasonic fingerprint sensor, IP68/IP69 rating, X-axis linear motor. Details to be confirmed at launch.</p><h2>Market Context & Global Availability</h2><p>The December 15 launch is confirmed for the Chinese market . Vivo has a history of rebranding its 'S' series for international markets; industry reports suggest the S50 series could launch globally later under different names, such as the Vivo V70 series in India.</p><p>The S50 Pro Mini, in particular, is generating interest as a "compact flagship," a niche segment that combines high-end specifications with a more manageable form factor. Its combination of the powerful Snapdragon 8 Gen 5 and a large 6,500mAh battery in a compact body is a key selling point.</p><h2>What to Expect at the Launch</h2><p>The official launch event on December 15 will provide final confirmation on:</p><p>Official pricing for all RAM and storage variants in China.</p><p>Complete camera specifications and software features.</p><p>Detailed design walkthrough and hands-on impressions.</p><p>Potential announcement regarding rollout to other regions.</p><p>With pre-orders already live in China, Vivo is poised for a significant year-end release aimed at photography enthusiasts and users seeking powerful performance in both standard and compact form factors.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 12:49:01 +0100</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://phonespecpro.com/img/vivo-s50-s50-pro-mini-launch-date-colors.webp" />
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">1716214692</guid>
			<title>Realme Narzo 90 Series 5G India Launch Announced, Will Be Available on Amazon</title>
			<link>https://phonespecpro.com/news/realme-narzo-90-series-5g-india-launch-amazon</link>
			<author>shedrack</author>
			<description>Realme Narzo 90 Series 5G launch in India confirmed via Amazon teaser. Two models, Narzo 90 Pro 5G &amp; 90x 5G, teased with big battery, fast charging &amp; camera upgrades. More details on Dec 9.</description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>By: <a href="https://phonespecpro.com/author/shedrack">Shedrack</a></p><p><img src="https://phonespecpro.com/img/realme-narzo-90-series-5g-india-launch-amazon.webp"></p><h2>Series Launch Confirmed for India</h2><p>Realme, in partnership with Amazon India, has officially begun teasing the launch of its next-generation Narzo 90 Series 5G smartphones. The teaser campaign confirms that the upcoming phones will be "Amazon Specials," meaning they will be available for purchase exclusively through the Amazon platform in India.</p><p>The launch comes months after the company introduced the Narzo 80 Series 5G in the country and signals a significant update to its popular budget-friendly 5G lineup.</p><h2>Two Distinct Models Teased</h2><p>A comic-style teaser on a dedicated Amazon microsite clearly reveals that the series will consist of two separate smartphone models with distinct rear camera designs.</p><p>Model 1 (Likely Narzo 90 Pro 5G) Features a camera layout reminiscent of the iPhone 16 Pro Max, similar to its predecessor, the Narzo 80 Pro 5G. This model is expected to be the higher-end variant of the series.</p><p>Model 2 (Likely Narzo 90x 5G) Sports a rectangular-shaped camera module with vertically-aligned lenses, a design language carried over from the Narzo 80x 5G.</p><p>Both phones are shown with flat frames and rounded corners , continuing Realme's recent design trends for a modern and uniform aesthetic.</p><h2>Teased Upgrades & Features</h2><p>While Realme has not revealed the full specifications, the Amazon microsite uses specific branding to hint at the key upgrades coming with the Narzo 90 Series.</p><p>Supercharged & Power Maxed Strongly suggests that the new models will pack larger batteries and support for faster charging technology compared to their predecessors.</p><p>Snap Sharp Points to significant improvements in the camera department , likely through upgraded sensors for sharper and better-quality photos.</p><p>Glow Maxed Indicates that the displays on both phones will have higher peak brightness levels , improving outdoor visibility.</p><h2>What Happens Next? Mark Your Calendar</h2><p>The current teaser campaign ends with a clear message for tech enthusiasts: "Gear Up for December 9. The Plot Gets Thicker."</p><p>This confirms that Realme will reveal more detailed information about the Narzo 90 Series 5G on December 9, 2025 . This next reveal is expected to include more concrete specifications, features, and potentially the official launch date for the smartphones in India.</p><p>Given the Amazon exclusive tag, consumers can expect the phones to be available for pre-orders or sale directly on Amazon India following the official announcement.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 12:49:00 +0100</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://phonespecpro.com/img/realme-narzo-90-series-5g-india-launch-amazon.webp" />
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">2417438569</guid>
			<title>OnePlus 15 Pre-Orders Go Live in the US — Pricing and Key Features Revealed</title>
			<link>https://phonespecpro.com/news/oneplus-15-us-pre-orders-pricing-features</link>
			<author>shedrack</author>
			<description>OnePlus 15 US pre-orders are now open, starting at $899. Get the Snapdragon 8 Elite Gen 5, a 7300mAh battery, and choose a free Watch 3, Buds Pro 3, or other accessory with your order.</description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>By: <a href="https://phonespecpro.com/author/shedrack">Shedrack</a></p><p><img src="https://phonespecpro.com/img/oneplus-15-us-pre-orders-pricing-features.webp"></p><h2>US Pre-Orders Officially Begin</h2><p>After a delay caused by the recent US government shutdown, the OnePlus 15 is now available for pre-order in the United States . Pre-orders went live on December 4, 2025, at 11 AM ET / 8 AM PT directly through OnePlus's official website.</p><p>The launch was initially postponed because the Federal Communications Commission (FCC) could not certify the device during the shutdown, which lasted from October 1 to November 12. With certification now complete, US customers can finally secure what OnePlus is calling a "two-generational upgrade" over its predecessor.</p><h2>US Pricing & Configurations</h2><p>The OnePlus 15 launches in the US with two clear configurations, with color availability linked to the storage tier.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 12:48:59 +0100</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://phonespecpro.com/img/oneplus-15-us-pre-orders-pricing-features.webp" />
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">3620434642</guid>
			<title>Realme 16 Pro Series Leak Reveals Launch Timeline, Storage Variants, Colors, Camera and Battery Specs</title>
			<link>https://phonespecpro.com/news/realme-16-pro-series-launch-specs-leak</link>
			<author>shedrack</author>
			<description>Major Realme 16 Pro series leaks: Expected India launch on January 6, 2026. Get leaked specs for the 16 Pro &amp; 16 Pro+, including a 200MP camera, 7000mAh battery, colors, storage options, and more.</description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Your ultimate destination for comprehensive phone specifications, comparisons, and reviews.</p><h3>Quick Links</h3><h3>About Us</h3><p>© 2025 PhoneSpec Pro. All rights reserved.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Mon, 08 Dec 2025 12:48:58 +0100</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://phonespecpro.com/img/realme-16-pro-series-launch-specs-leak.webp" />
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">1315224463</guid>
			<title>Samsung Galaxy Devices Now Available on Instamart With 10-Minute Instant Delivery in India</title>
			<link>https://phonespecpro.com/news/samsung-instamart-10-minute-delivery-india</link>
			<author>shedrack</author>
			<description>Samsung has partnered with Swiggy's Instamart to offer 10-minute instant delivery of its Galaxy smartphones, tablets, smartwatches, and accessories across major Indian metro cities.</description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>By: <a href="https://phonespecpro.com/author/shedrack">Shedrack</a></p><p><img src="https://phonespecpro.com/img/samsung-instamart-10-minute-delivery-india.webp"></p><h2>Breaking News: Ultra-Fast Tech Delivery Lands in India</h2><p>In a significant move that redefines tech retail convenience, Samsung India has announced a strategic partnership with Swiggy's quick-commerce platform, Instamart, to deliver a wide range of Galaxy devices to customers' doorsteps in approximately 10 minutes. This expansion of Samsung's omnichannel strategy brings smartphones, tablets, smartwatches, wireless earbuds, and accessories into the realm of instant gratification previously reserved for groceries and daily essentials.</p><p>Announced on December 5, 2025, this partnership represents a major shift in how consumers can purchase electronics in India. With this collaboration, customers in select metro cities can now order Galaxy products through the Instamart app and receive them within minutes, providing unprecedented convenience for urgent needs like replacing a lost phone or grabbing last-minute travel accessories.</p><h2>Partnership Details and Available Products</h2><p>The Samsung-Instamart partnership expands on an earlier initiative that began with Galaxy smartphones earlier in 2025. The service has now been extended to include a broader range of Galaxy devices, creating what Samsung describes as a more comprehensive "Galaxy experience" available in minutes.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://phonespecpro.com/img/samsung-instamart-10-minute-delivery-india.webp" />
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">4097534494</guid>
			<title>OnePlus 15R Spotted on Geekbench With 12GB RAM and Android 16</title>
			<link>https://phonespecpro.com/news/oneplus-15r-geekbench-leak</link>
			<author>shedrack</author>
			<description>The upcoming OnePlus 15R, set for a December 17 launch, has appeared on Geekbench with the new Snapdragon 8 Gen 5 chipset, 12GB RAM, and Android 16.</description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>By: <a href="https://phonespecpro.com/author/shedrack">Shedrack</a></p><p><img src="https://phonespecpro.com/img/oneplus-15r-geekbench-leak.webp"></p><h2>Benchmark Leak Reveals Key Specs Ahead of Launch</h2><p>With less than two weeks to go until its official unveiling, the highly anticipated OnePlus 15R has made a telling appearance on the Geekbench benchmarking database. The listing, first spotted on December 5, 2025, provides the clearest look yet at the core hardware powering OnePlus's upcoming "value flagship" .</p><p>The device, identified by the model number CPH2767 , is widely believed to be the global variant of the OnePlus 15R, set to launch in India, Europe, and North America on December 17, 2025 . The benchmark confirms it will be the world's first smartphone to ship with Qualcomm's new Snapdragon 8 Gen 5 chipset, paired with 12GB of RAM and running Android 16 out of the box .</p>]]></content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://phonespecpro.com/img/oneplus-15r-geekbench-leak.webp" />
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">1503641719</guid>
			<title>Nothing Phone 3a Lite Goes on Sale in India — Price, Launch Offers, and Full Specifications</title>
			<link>https://phonespecpro.com/news/nothing-phone-3a-lite-india-sale-price-specs</link>
			<author>shedrack</author>
			<description>The Nothing Phone 3a Lite is now available for purchase in India starting at ₹20,999 with launch offers on Flipkart.</description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>By: <a href="https://phonespecpro.com/author/shedrack">Shedrack</a></p><p><img src="https://phonespecpro.com/img/nothing-phone-3a-lite-india-sale-price-specs.webp"></p><h2>Nothing Phone 3a Lite Now Available in India</h2><p>Nothing's latest mid-range smartphone, the Phone 3a Lite , has officially gone on sale in India as of December 5, 2025. The phone, which was initially launched in the country on November 27, aims to deliver the brand's signature design language, clean software, and unique features at a more accessible price point.</p><p>Sales have commenced through major online and offline channels, including Flipkart, Vijay Sales, and Croma, allowing customers across India to purchase the device. The launch is accompanied by several introductory offers from banks and e-commerce platforms, making the phone an even more compelling proposition in the competitive sub-₹25,000 segment.</p><h2>Price in India and Launch Offers</h2><p>The Nothing Phone 3a Lite is positioned aggressively in the Indian market, with a starting price that brings key features of the Nothing ecosystem to a wider audience.</p><p>Key Launch Offers Instant discount of ₹1,000 for ICICI Bank and OneCard customers. Additional cashback offers on Flipkart Axis Bank and SBI cards.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://phonespecpro.com/img/nothing-phone-3a-lite-india-sale-price-specs.webp" />
		</item>
		<item>
			<guid isPermaLink="false">1227457853</guid>
			<title>Motorola Edge 70 “Cloud Dancer” Special Edition Announced with Swarovski Crystals</title>
			<link>https://phonespecpro.com/news/motorola-edge-70-cloud-dancer-special-edition</link>
			<author>shedrack</author>
			<description>Motorola has unveiled a luxurious special edition of its Edge 70 smartphone, finished in Pantone's 2026 Color of the Year, Cloud Dancer, and adorned with Swarovski crystals.</description>
			<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>By: <a href="https://phonespecpro.com/author/shedrack">Shedrack</a></p><p><img src="https://phonespecpro.com/img/motorola-edge-70-cloud-dancer-special-edition.webp"></p><h2>A Fusion of Color, Craftsmanship, and Calm</h2><p>Motorola has unveiled a new, highly exclusive special edition of its flagship Edge 70 smartphone, designed in collaboration with two iconic brands: Pantone and Swarovski. Dubbed the "Cloud Dancer" edition, this phone is finished in Pantone's official Color of the Year for 2026 and features carefully embedded Swarovski crystals on its back panel, marking it as a premium object of design as much as a piece of technology.</p><p>The launch continues Motorola's multi-year partnership with Pantone and expands its design-focused "Brilliant Collection" , which emphasizes meticulous craftsmanship and luxury. Motorola frames this edition as a direct response to digital overload, aiming to create a device that embodies "calm confidence and refined expression".</p><h2>Design Philosophy & Collaborative Details</h2><p>The core of this special edition is the Pantone 11-4201 Cloud Dancer color. Described as an "airy white hue," Pantone states it communicates "clarity over clutter, softness over spectacle, and presence over pressure," acting as a symbol of calm and serenity.</p><p>Color Pantone 11-4201 Cloud Dancer – The Pantone Color of the Year 2026.</p><p>Luxury Accents Features crystals by Swarovski embedded into the back panel design for an "ethereal touch".</p><p>Design Collection Part of Motorola's Brilliant Collection , focused on timeless luxury and craftsmanship.</p><p>Back Material Leather-inspired back with a quilted pattern, providing a tactile contrast to the crystals.</p><p>Executive Statement “Cloud Dancer reflects a new kind of design mindset, one that celebrates simplicity as strength," said Ruben Castano, VP of Design at Motorola.</p><h2>Full Phone Specifications</h2><p>While the exterior is unique, the Cloud Dancer edition retains the complete high-end hardware of the standard Edge 70 . This includes its claim to being one of the thinnest phones in its category and a powerful triple-camera system.</p><p>Dimensions & Build 5.99mm thin , 159g weight. Aircraft-grade aluminum frame with Gorilla Glass 7i. IP68/IP69 water resistance and MIL-STD-810H durability.</p><p>Display 6.67-inch pOLED , 1220 x 2712 pixels, 120Hz refresh rate, HDR10+, up to 4500 nits peak brightness, Pantone Validated for color accuracy.</p><p>Platform Qualcomm Snapdragon 7 Gen 4 chipset. 12GB RAM with 512GB storage (non-expandable). Runs Android 16 with 4 major OS update promise.</p><p>Camera System Triple 50MP cameras:</p><p>4K video recording on all sensors.</p><p>Battery & Charging 4800mAh silicon-carbon battery. 68W wired TurboPower charging (hours of power in 15 mins). 15W wireless charging support.</p><p>Audio & Connectivity Stereo speakers with Dolby Atmos. No 3.5mm jack. Wi-Fi 6E, Bluetooth 5.4, NFC, 5G connectivity.</p><h2>Availability, Pricing, and Market Context</h2><p>Motorola has announced that the Edge 70 Cloud Dancer special edition will be available in select markets worldwide , but specific countries, release dates, and most importantly, pricing have not yet been disclosed .</p><p>For reference, the standard Motorola Edge 70 (12GB/512GB) launched in the UK at a price of £695 (~₹80,000) and in Europe starting from €799 (~₹81,000) . Given the luxury materials and exclusive nature of this edition, it is expected to command a premium over the standard model.</p><p>This special edition arrives shortly after the Edge 70's initial launch in October 2025, where it was offered in three other Pantone-curated colors: Gadget Gray, Lily Pad, and Bronze Green. The collaboration underscores a growing trend of smartphone makers partnering with fashion and luxury brands to create distinctive, design-led devices for niche audiences.</p><h2>Final Thoughts</h2><p>The Motorola Edge 70 Cloud Dancer edition is a bold statement in a market often focused on raw specs. It successfully transforms the already sleek Edge 70 into a unique luxury accessory. The combination of the meaningful Pantone color story and the physical sparkle of Swarovski crystals creates a phone that is designed to stand out through subtlety and craftsmanship.</p><p>Bottom Line: This phone is not for everyone—it's for the buyer who prioritizes design, exclusivity, and a philosophical alignment with a calmer digital aesthetic as much as they do premium performance and camera capabilities. If the standard Edge 70's thin profile and capable cameras already appealed to you, this special edition offers a way to own that technology in a truly one-of-a-kind package.</p>]]></content:encoded>
			<pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
			<enclosure url="https://phonespecpro.com/img/motorola-edge-70-cloud-dancer-special-edition.webp" />
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>